(Sheldon:)I don't care!
I'm losin' it, man!
(Leonard:)Why don't we play this smart?
(Leonard:)Try a little
"good goblin, bad goblin."
(Priya:)Oh, dear Lord.
(Howard:)Nah, I think we have
to be more subtle.
(Raj:)Okay, I see where
this is going.
(Raj:)Fine, I'll have
sex with him.
(Leonard:)That's not where it was going.
(laughs)
Good, because
I would hate that.
(Priya:)Leonard, you're busy--
let's talk tomorrow.
(Leonard:)Oh, wait.
(Leonard:)- Hang on. Are you upset?
- No, no, I think
(Priya:)it's sexy to date a boy
trapped in a man's body.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Leonard:)Good, good.
(Leonard:)I'll tell you
what happens.
(door closes)
And people think I
don't get sarcasm.
(door opens)
(Amy:)Well, well, well.
(Amy:)Look who it is.
(Penny:)Okay, be nice.
(Priya:)Hello.
(Penny:)Hi. We're just
heading out for a drink.
(Amy:)Because I do that now.